# **Greg Harris Harris**

Full Stack Web Developer

Full-stack Web Developer with a background in digital artwork and graphic design who recently finished a certification through the University of Washington. Coding experience using languages like HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, and technologies like React and Node. Strength is with backend web development, building out and maintaining databases. Work history with retail and customer service, provided for operating well with a team, mentorship, goal setting, and ability to delegate tasks to ensure project completion. Passionate about incorporating creative and artistic abilities to design logos, layouts, and frameworks for various web applications.



support@resumethatworks.com



1-888-463-7563



100 West 33rd Street, New York, NY 10001, United States, Suite 301.



resumethatworks.com/



### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Web Developer - Projects University of Washington

12/2020 - Present

Bellevue, Washington, United

My Mini Gallery | https://github.com/Amal31497/My-Mini-Gallery | https://myminigallery.herokuapp.com/This web application allows users to discover, view and share artwork with each other online. Worked on building out the database to save and encrypt user accounts or store their images and information. MongoDB | Mongoose | HTML | CSS | JS | Bootstrap | ReactJS

#### **Produce/Grocery Clerk** Kroger

09/2006 - Present



**SKILLS** 

Web Development



## **EDUCATION**

Certificate, Full Stack Web Development University of Washington

12/2020 - 06/2021

Study Program Edmonds College

2008 - 2010